Department of Physical Education and Athletics Records UA046
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1871 -- 2012; 1950 -- 1999; UA046.002; 26.65 Linear Feet; 23 Audiovisual Object(s)
  - Distinguished Achievement Award, 1994, Homecoming, John Hannah and Nancy Kerrigan, Access Copy, UA046.002.118.001 (Box 118)
    ACCESS COPY- see UA046/002-117 for preservation copy. [Transcribed from original video case]: A
  - Distinguished Achievement Award, 1995, Intro to Jackie MacMullan and Jim Lonborg, UA046.002.119.001 (Box 119)
    [Transcribed from original video case]: Tufts Jumbo Club, Hi-lites, A, Yellow circle sticker
  - Distinguished Achievement Award, October 27, 1995, Jim Lonburg and Jackie MacMullan, UA046.002.120.001 (Box 120)
    [Transcribed from orginal video case]: Tufts Jumbo Club, Needs Hi-lite footage, B, Yellow circle sticker
  - Distinguished Achievement Award, 1996, UA046.002.121.001 (Box 121)
    [Transcibed from original video case]: Hi lites, A
  - Distinguished Achievement Award, 1996, Johnny Pesky and Gino Cappelletti, Preservation Copy, UA046.002.122.001 (Box 122)
    PRESERVATION COPY- use UA046/002-123 for access. [Transcibed from original video case]: Tufts Jumbo Club 1996, B
  - Distinguished Achievement Award, 1996, Johnny Pesky and Gino Cappelletti, Access Copy, UA046.002.123.001 (Box 123)
    ACCESS COPY- for preservation copy see UA046/002-122. [Transcribed from original video case]: Tufts Jumbo Club, C.
  - Distinguished Achievement Award, 1997, Honoring Johnnie Grinnell and Bud Collins, Preservation Copy, UA046.002.124.001 (Box 124)
    Preservation Copy- for access copy use UA046/002-125. [Transcribed from original video case]: Tufts Jumbo Club, A, Master
  - Distinguished Achievement Awards, 1997, Johnnie Grinnell and Bud Collins, Access Copy, UA046.002.125.001 (Box 125)
    Access Copy- for preservation copy see UA046/002-124. [Transcribed from original video case]: Tufts Jumbo Club, B
  - Distinguished Achievement Award, 1999, Jumbo Celebration, Story of Jumbo Homecoming, Preservation Copy, UA046.002.126.001 (Box 126)
    PRESERVATION COPY- for access copy use UA046/002-127. [Transcribed from original video case]: only
  - Distinguished Achievement Award, 1999, Story of Jumbo Homecoming (October), Access Copy, UA046.002.127.001 (Box 127)
    ACCESS COPY- for preservation copy see UA046/002-127. [Transcribed from original video case]: only
  - Distinguished Achievement Award, 1999, Missing Jumbo Footage (story), Preservation Copy, UA046.002.128.001 (Box 128)
    Preservation Copy, for access copy use UA046/002-129. [Transcribed from original video case]: Tufts, B
  - Distinguished Achievement Award, 1999, Missing Jumbo Story Footage, Access Copy, UA046.002.129.001 (Box 129)
    Access Copy, for preservation copy see UA046/002-128. [Transcribed from original video case]: Tufts, A
  - Distinguished Achievement Award, Aug. 24, 2001, Preservation Copy, UA046.002.130.001 (Box 130)
    Preservation copy- digital format, For access copy use UA046/002-131
  - Distinguished Achievement Award, A Jumbo Celebration, Aug. 24, 2001, Access Copy, UA046.002.131.001 (Box 131)
    Access Copy, for preservation copy see UA046/002-130
  - End of Season Reports Fall, 1987 -- 1988; UA046.002.132.00001 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Winter, 1987 -- 1988; UA046.002.132.00002 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Spring, 1987 -- 1988; UA046.002.132.00003 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Fall, 1988 -- 1989; UA046.002.132.00004 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Winter, 1988 -- 1989; UA046.002.132.00005 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Spring, 1988 -- 1989; UA046.002.132.00006 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Spring with Rocky's Highlights, 1988 -- 1989; UA046.002.132.00007 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Fall/Winter/Spring, 1988 -- 1989; UA046.002.132.00008 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Fall, 1989 -- 1990; UA046.002.132.00009 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Winter, 1989 -- 1990; UA046.002.132.00010 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Spring, 1989 -- 1990; UA046.002.132.00011 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Fall, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.002.132.00012 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Winter, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.002.132.00013 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Spring, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.002.132.00014 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Fall, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.002.132.00015 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Winter, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.002.132.00016 (Box 132)
  - End of Season Reports Spring, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.002.132.00017 (Box 132)
  - Hooker v. Tufts, UA046.002.132.00018 (Box 132)
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - Interdepartmental Requisitions, 2000; UA046.002.132.00019 (Box 132)
  - Interdepartmental Requisitions, 2000; UA046.002.132.00020 (Box 132)
  - Pawlak v. Tufts, UA046.002.132.00021 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards, 1908 -- 1935; UA046.002.132.00022 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Fall, 1987 -- 1988; UA046.002.132.00023 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Winter, 1987 -- 1988; UA046.002.132.00024 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Spring, 1987 -- 1988; UA046.002.132.00025 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Fall, 1988 -- 1989; UA046.002.132.00026 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Winter, 1988 -- 1989; UA046.002.132.00027 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Spring, 1988 -- 1989; UA046.002.132.00028 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Fall, 1989 -- 1990; UA046.002.132.00029 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Winter, 1989 -- 1990; UA046.002.132.00030 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Spring, 1989 -- 1990; UA046.002.132.00031 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Fall, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.002.132.00032 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Winter, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.002.132.00033 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Spring, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.002.132.00034 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Fall, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.002.132.00035 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Winter, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.002.132.00036 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Spring, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.002.132.00037 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Winter, 1992; UA046.002.132.00038 (Box 132)
  - Records and Awards Spring, 1992; UA046.002.132.00039 (Box 132)
  - Title IX Rewrite, 1974 -- 1975; UA046.002.132.00040 (Box 132)
  - Title IX Information, 1978 -- 1979; UA046.002.132.00041 (Box 132)
  - Title IX Information, 1978 -- 1979; UA046.002.132.00042 (Box 132)
  - Title IX Final Report, 1978 -- 1980; UA046.002.132.00043 (Box 132)
  - Title IX, 1979 -- 1980; UA046.002.132.00044 (Box 132)
  - Title IX, 1980; UA046.002.132.00045 (Box 132)
  - Baseball agreements, contracts between Tufts and other schools, 1935 -- 1936; UA046.002.141.00001 (Box 141)
  - Baseball agreements, contracts between Tufts and other schools, 1936 -- 1937; UA046.002.141.00002 (Box 141)
  - Baseball agreements, contracts between Tufts and other schools, 1934 -- 1957; UA046.002.141.00003 (Box 141)
  - NCAA FH, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.002.164.00001 (Box 164)
  - All American FH, 1990; UA046.002.164.00002 (Box 164)
  - College field hockey coaches poll, 1989; UA046.002.164.00003 (Box 164)
  - FH NCAA poll, 1990; UA046.002.164.00004 (Box 164)
  - Field hockey poll NCAA, 1989; UA046.002.164.00005 (Box 164)
  - Field hockey regional poll, 1988; UA046.002.164.00006 (Box 164)
  - Field hockey regional and national poll, 1987; UA046.002.164.00007 (Box 164)
  - ECAC and NIAC field hockey, 1988; UA046.002.164.00008 (Box 164)
  - NCAA and regional hockey poll, 1986; UA046.002.164.00009 (Box 164)
  - Stat sheet field hockey, 1986; UA046.002.164.00010 (Box 164)
  - Field hockey intercollegiate sports records and awards fall, 2000; UA046.002.164.00011 (Box 164)
  - Women's lacrosse IWLCA regional all-American selections, 1995; UA046.002.164.00012 (Box 164)
  - Men's lacrosse awards, 2000; UA046.002.164.00013 (Box 164)
  - Letter winners, 1973 -- 1982; UA046.002.164.00014 (Box 164)
  - Jumbo club story, 1988 -- 2003; UA046.002.164.00015 (Box 164)
  - Kitteredge family donation, 2008; UA046.002.164.00016 (Box 164)
  - Winter sports freshman numerals, 1957 -- 1958; UA046.002.164.00017 (Box 164)
  - Tufts lacrosse history, 1950 -- 1960; UA046.002.164.00018 (Box 164)
  - Men's lacrosse awards, 2007; UA046.002.164.00019 (Box 164)
  - Project planning report athletic facilty expansion, 1997; UA046.002.164.00020 (Box 164)
  - Project planning report appedices athletic facilty expansion, 1997; UA046.002.164.00021 (Box 164)
  - New field house binder 1of 4, 1999; UA046.002.164.00022 (Box 164)
  - New field house binder 2 of 4, 1999; UA046.002.164.00023 (Box 164)
  - New field house binder 3 of 4, 1998; UA046.002.164.00024 (Box 164)
  - New field house binder 4 of 4, 1997; UA046.002.164.00025 (Box 164)
  - Alumni field renovation binder, 2004; UA046.002.164.00026 (Box 164)
  - Athletics committee, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.002.164.00027 (Box 164)
  - Title IX articles, 1997 -- 1999; UA046.002.164.00028 (Box 164)
  - Injury rate articles, 1997; UA046.002.164.00029 (Box 164)
  - Athletics committee, 1995 -- 1997; UA046.002.164.00030 (Box 164)
  - Athletics Glaser info, 1996 -- 1997; UA046.002.164.00031 (Box 164)
  - Sports club regulations, 1996 -- 1997; UA046.002.164.00032 (Box 164)
  - Ruby, 1996 -- 1998; UA046.002.164.00033 (Box 164)
  - Athletics committee, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.002.164.00034 (Box 164)
  - NESCAC, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.002.164.00035 (Box 164)
  - Baseball, 1964 -- 1974; UA046.002.164.00036 (Box 164)
  - Varsity soccer records, 1965 -- 1973; UA046.002.164.00037 (Box 164)
  - Fall weekly results binder, 1990; UA046.002.164.00038 (Box 164)
  - Sports information binder 1 of 2, 1988 -- 1989; UA046.002.164.00039 (Box 164)
  - Sports information binder 2 of 2, 1988 -- 1989; UA046.002.164.00040 (Box 164)
  - Awards binder 1 of 2, 1980 -- 1984; UA046.002.164.00041 (Box 164)
  - Awards binder 2 of 2, 1980 -- 1984; UA046.002.164.00042 (Box 164)
  - Awards binder 1 of 2, 1976 -- 1984; UA046.002.164.00043 (Box 164)
  - Awards binder 2 of 2, 1978 -- 1986; UA046.002.164.00044 (Box 164)
  - Sports standings, 2000 -- 2009; UA046.002.164.00045 (Box 164)
  - Baseball, 1920 -- 1957; UA046.002.164.00046 (Box 164)
  - Newspaper clippings women's swim team, 1982 -- 1987; UA046.002.164.00047 (Box 164)
  - Newspaper clippings women's swim team, 1983 -- 1984; UA046.002.164.00048 (Box 164)
  - Project Manual for Athletic Facilities Renovation and Expansion, Volume II of II [1 of 3], 2008; UA046.002.165.00001 (Box 165)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Project Manual for Athletic Facilities Renovation and Expansion, Volume II of II [2 of 3], 2008; UA046.002.165.00002 (Box 165)
  - Project Manual for Athletic Facilities Renovation and Expansion, Volume II of II [3 of 3], 2008; UA046.002.165.00003 (Box 165)
  - Department of Athletics: Annual Report, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.002.165.00004 (Box 165)
  - Department of Athletics: Annual Report, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.002.165.00005 (Box 165)
  - Annual Report Coordinator's Copy, 1994 -- 1995; UA046.002.165.00006 (Box 165)
  - Annual Report Coordinator's Copy, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.002.165.00007 (Box 165)
  - Tufts University's Women's Sports Celebration: Commemorative Program, 1995 -- 1999; UA046.002.165.00008 (Box 165)
  - Project Plannning Report Phase 3A/3B, 1997; UA046.002.165.00009 (Box 165)
  - Summer Programs (Binders), 1991 -- 1996; UA046.002.165.00010 (Box 165)
  - Athletic Committee Minutes of Meetings (Binder) [1 of 2], 1978 -- 1981; UA046.002.165.00011 (Box 165)
  - Athletic Committee Minutes of Meetings (Binder) [2 of 2], 1978 -- 1981; UA046.002.165.00012 (Box 165)
  - Athletic Committee Minutes of Meetings (Binder) [1 of 2], 1981 -- 1984; UA046.002.165.00013 (Box 165)
  - Athletic Committee Minutes of Meetings (Binder) [2 of 2], 1981 -- 1984; UA046.002.165.00014 (Box 165)
  - Athletic Committee Minutes of Meetings (Binder) [1 of 2], 1984 -- 1990; UA046.002.165.00015 (Box 165)
  - Athletic Committee Minutes of Meetings (Binder) [2 of 2], 1984 -- 1990; UA046.002.165.00016 (Box 165)
  - Athletic Committee Minutes of Meetings (Binder), 1990 -- 1994; UA046.002.165.00017 (Box 165)
  - GBC Meetings, 1986 -- 1987; UA046.002.165.00018 (Box 165)
    Greater Boston Conference
  - Overseers (Binder) [1 of 2], 1990 -- 1995; UA046.002.165.00019 (Box 165)
  - Overseers (Binder) [2 of 2], 1990 -- 1995; UA046.002.165.00020 (Box 165)
  - Overseers (Binder) [1 of 2], 1988 -- 1990; UA046.002.165.00021 (Box 165)
  - Overseers (Binder) [2 of 2], 1988 -- 1990; UA046.002.165.00022 (Box 165)
  - Athletic Facilities Programming Study, 1989; UA046.002.165.00023 (Box 165)
  - Tufts Athletics Complex, UA046.002.165.00024 (Box 165)
  - Athletic Facility Schematic Design Report [1 of 2], 1994; UA046.002.165.00025 (Box 165)
  - Athletic Facility Schematic Design Report [2 of 2], 1994; UA046.002.165.00026 (Box 165)
  - Rosters, 2005 -- 2006; UA046.002.165.00027 (Box 165)
  - Rosters, 2004 -- 2005; UA046.002.165.00028 (Box 165)
  - Rosters, 2003; UA046.002.165.00029 (Box 165)
  - Rosters, 2002; UA046.002.165.00030 (Box 165)
  - Team Rosters, 1988; UA046.002.165.00031 (Box 165)
  - Athletics letterhead, UA046.002.166.00001 (Box 166)
  - Cousens gymanasium complex plans, 1984; UA046.002.166.00002 (Box 166)
  - Cousens expansion Tully plans, 1986 -- 1989; UA046.002.166.00003 (Box 166)
  - Proposed master plan Cousens Athletic Complex, 1988; UA046.002.166.00004 (Box 166)
  - Athletic Complex: making a difference, UA046.002.166.00005 (Box 166)
  - Study and budgets for the Athletic Fields and Baronian Field house, 1985 -- 1986; UA046.002.166.00006 (Box 166)
  - Athletics Facilities Programing Study, draft, 1989; UA046.002.166.00007 (Box 166)
  - Reily Student Recreation Center workshop, December 4, 1988; UA046.002.166.00008 (Box 166)
  - Intercollegiate Athletic Complex Compettition University Designs, 1980; UA046.002.166.00009 (Box 166)
  - Lockers, UA046.002.166.00010 (Box 166)
  - Cousens gymnasium, 1984; UA046.002.166.00011 (Box 166)
  - Feasibility study proposed Cousens Complex additions and alterations1977, UA046.002.166.00012 (Box 166)
  - Cousens renovations, 1977 -- 1979; UA046.002.166.00013 (Box 166)
  - Cousens alterations, 1973 -- 1980; UA046.002.166.00014 (Box 166)
  - Intercollegiate sports records and awards, 1984 -- 1988; UA046.002.166.00015 (Box 166)
  - Soccer rosters, 1966 -- 1990; UA046.002.166.00016 (Box 166)
  - List of athletes who are missing from student records and awards list, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.002.166.00017 (Box 166)
  - Basketball, 1950 -- 1991; UA046.002.166.00018 (Box 166)
  - Cousens expansion 1 of 2, 1985 -- 1990; UA046.002.166.00019 (Box 166)
  - Cousens expansion 2 of 2, 1982 -- 1990; UA046.002.166.00020 (Box 166)
  - Jackson gym conversion, 1996 -- 1997; UA046.002.166.00021 (Box 166)
  - Dance studio conversion, 1992 -- 1993; UA046.002.166.00022 (Box 166)
  - Phase II project, 1996; UA046.002.166.00023 (Box 166)
  - Athletics Halligan renovations, 1994 -- 1995; UA046.002.166.00024 (Box 166)
  - Halligan, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.002.166.00025 (Box 166)
  - Office projects, 1993; UA046.002.166.00026 (Box 166)
  - Hooper lounge, 1993; UA046.002.166.00027 (Box 166)
  - New dormitory, 1989 -- 1990; UA046.002.166.00028 (Box 166)
  - Fitness center project, 1993; UA046.002.166.00029 (Box 166)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 1 of 3], 1995 -- 1997; UA046.002.167.00001 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 2 of 3], 1995 -- 1997; UA046.002.167.00002 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 3 of 3], 1995 -- 1997; UA046.002.167.00003 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, front matter], 1997 -- 1999; UA046.002.167.00004 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 1 of 3], 1997 -- 1999; UA046.002.167.00005 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 2 of 3], 1997 -- 1999; UA046.002.167.00006 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 3 of 3], 1997 -- 1999; UA046.002.167.00007 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, front matter], 1993 -- 1995; UA046.002.167.00008 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 1 of 4], 1993 -- 1995; UA046.002.167.00009 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 2 of 4], 1993 -- 1995; UA046.002.167.00010 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 3 of 4], 1993 -- 1995; UA046.002.167.00011 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 4 of 4], 1993 -- 1995; UA046.002.167.00012 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 1 of 4], 1990 -- 1993; UA046.002.167.00013 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 2 of 4], 1990 -- 1993; UA046.002.167.00014 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 3 of 4], 1990 -- 1993; UA046.002.167.00015 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 4 of 4], 1990 -- 1993; UA046.002.167.00016 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 1 of 2], 1996; UA046.002.167.00017 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 2 of 2], 1996; UA046.002.167.00018 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 1 of 2], 2000 -- 2004; UA046.002.167.00019 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 2 of 2], 2000 -- 2004; UA046.002.167.00020 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 1 of 2], 1999 -- 2000; UA046.002.167.00021 (Box 167)
  - NESCAC [binder, folder 2 of 2], 1999 -- 2000; UA046.002.167.00022 (Box 167)
  - Post Season Report Part 1 [binder], 1974 -- 1980; UA046.002.168.00001 (Box 168)
  - Post Season Report Part 2 [binder], 1974 -- 1980; UA046.002.168.00002 (Box 168)
  - Post Season Reports Part 1 [1 of 2, binder], 1981 -- 1987; UA046.002.168.00003 (Box 168)
  - Post Season Reports Part 1 [2 of 2, binder], 1981 -- 1987; UA046.002.168.00004 (Box 168)
  - Post Season Reports Part 2 [binder], 1981 -- 1986; UA046.002.168.00005 (Box 168)
  - Post Season Reports [1 of 2, binder], 1988 -- 1994; UA046.002.168.00006 (Box 168)
  - Post Season Reports [2 of 2, binder], 1988 -- 1994; UA046.002.168.00007 (Box 168)
  - Post Season Reports [1 of 2, binder], 1994 -- 2001; UA046.002.168.00008 (Box 168)
  - Post Season Reports [2 of 2, binder], 1994 -- 2001; UA046.002.168.00009 (Box 168)
  - Post Season Reports, 2001 -- 2008; UA046.002.168.00010 (Box 168)
  - Athletic Department Awards [binder], 2005; UA046.002.168.00011 (Box 168)
  - Records and Awards [binder], 1954 -- 1967; UA046.002.168.00012 (Box 168)
  - Records and Awards [binder], 1967 -- 1975; UA046.002.168.00013 (Box 168)
  - Records and Awards [binder], 1975 -- 1981; UA046.002.168.00014 (Box 168)
  - Records and Awards [1 of 2, binder], 1981 -- 1988; UA046.002.168.00015 (Box 168)
  - Records and Awards [2 of 2, binder], 1981 -- 1988; UA046.002.168.00016 (Box 168)
  - Records and Awards [1 of 2, binder], 1982 -- 1988; UA046.002.168.00017 (Box 168)
  - Records and Awards [2 of 2, binder], 1982 -- 1988; UA046.002.168.00018 (Box 168)
  - Department of athletics annual report, 1998 -- 1999; UA046.002.169.00001 (Box 169)
  - Athletics basic principles and calendar, 1982 -- 1983; UA046.002.169.00002 (Box 169)
  - Woodworth memorial, 1990 -- 1993; UA046.002.169.00003 (Box 169)
  - Kuhl Award, 1992 -- 1993; UA046.002.169.00004 (Box 169)
  - Murray Kenney Award, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.002.169.00005 (Box 169)
  - Swim award gift, 1989 -- 1993; UA046.002.169.00006 (Box 169)
  - Grimm (swim) Award, 1990 -- 1993; UA046.002.169.00007 (Box 169)
  - John Baronian, 1994 -- 1997; UA046.002.169.00008 (Box 169)
  - Carzo cage, 2002; UA046.002.169.00009 (Box 169)
  - Rocky Carzo correspondence, 1973 -- 2003; UA046.002.169.00010 (Box 169)
  - Calvalcade of champions, 1982 -- 1985; UA046.002.169.00011 (Box 169)
  - Distinguished service award (alumni council), 1992 -- 2001; UA046.002.169.00012 (Box 169)
  - Chase I.M. gym dedication, 1996; UA046.002.169.00013 (Box 169)
  - Ellis oval scoreboard, 1974 -- 1981; UA046.002.169.00014 (Box 169)
  - New fieldhouse and intramural gym, 1996 -- 1998; UA046.002.169.00015 (Box 169)
  - Gantcher, 1998 -- 1999; UA046.002.169.00016 (Box 169)
  - Baronian gate, 1987 -- 1991; UA046.002.169.00017 (Box 169)
  - Ellis oval gate dedication, 2001; UA046.002.169.00018 (Box 169)
  - Track dedication, 1990; UA046.002.169.00019 (Box 169)
  - Human performance - fitness center, 1994 -- 1998; UA046.002.169.00020 (Box 169)
  - List of American football coaches association members attending first banquet December 27, 1922; UA046.002.169.00021 (Box 169)
  - Football and international camps 1 of 2, 1992 -- 1998; UA046.002.169.00022 (Box 169)
  - Football and international camps 2 of 2, 1992; UA046.002.169.00023 (Box 169)
  - Art and Margot Harrison, 1966 -- 1998; UA046.002.169.00024 (Box 169)
  - Judge Dave Harrison 60th celebration, 1993 -- 1998; UA046.002.169.00025 (Box 169)
  - Honorary degrees, 1993 -- 1997; UA046.002.169.00026 (Box 169)
  - Jackson gym repairs maintenance, 1979 -- 1996; UA046.002.169.00027 (Box 169)
  - Jumbo club award winners- 1985 on, 1999 -- 2004; UA046.002.169.00028 (Box 169)
  - Mission statement, 1984 -- 1990; UA046.002.169.00029 (Box 169)
  - Sports museum, 1992; UA046.002.169.00030 (Box 169)
  - Tisch library dedication sports forum, 1996; UA046.002.169.00031 (Box 169)
  - NCAA fall champs, 2006; UA046.002.169.00032 (Box 169)
  - Crew, 1991 -- 1996; UA046.002.169.00033 (Box 169)
  - Crew riverside boathouse, 1988 -- 2003; UA046.002.169.00034 (Box 169)
  - Sailing pavillion, 1985 -- 1993; UA046.002.169.00035 (Box 169)
  - Title IX 1 of 2, 1996 -- 2002; UA046.002.169.00036 (Box 169)
  - Title IX 2 of 2, 1977 -- 1996; UA046.002.169.00037 (Box 169)
  - Title IX, 1995; UA046.002.169.00038 (Box 169)
  - Unfoldered title IX materials 1 of 3, 1995; UA046.002.169.00039 (Box 169)
  - Unfoldered title IX materials 2 of 3, 1995; UA046.002.169.00040 (Box 169)
  - Unfoldered title IX materials 3 of 3, 1997 -- 2001; UA046.002.169.00041 (Box 169)
  - New England Small College Athletic Conference gender equality raw data compilation, 1994; UA046.002.169.00042 (Box 169)
  - Haverford Group Beginning [binder, folder 1 of 2], 1987 -- 1998; UA046.002.170.00001 (Box 170)
  - Haverford Group Beginning [binder, folder 2 of 2], 1987 -- 1998; UA046.002.170.00002 (Box 170)
  - Indoor Long Range Plan [binder, front matter], 1989; UA046.002.170.00003 (Box 170)
  - Indoor Long Range Plan [binder], 1989; UA046.002.170.00004 (Box 170)
  - 1953 Lacrosse Reunion Clipping, 2005; UA046.002.170.00005 (Box 170)
  - Misc Clippings (Bloom), 1986; UA046.002.170.00006 (Box 170)
  - NESCAC Study [binder, front matter], 1996; UA046.002.170.00007 (Box 170)
  - NESCAC Study [binder], 1996; UA046.002.170.00008 (Box 170)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Tufts Athletics, 1954 -- 2005; UA046.002.170.00009 (Box 170)
  - Club sports [binder], 1999 -- 2003; UA046.002.170.00010 (Box 170)
  - Outdoor Track [binder, folder 1 of 2], 1989; UA046.002.170.00011 (Box 170)
  - Outdoor Track [binder, folder 2 of 2], 1989; UA046.002.170.00012 (Box 170)
  - World Cup and Olympics (Boston), 1992; UA046.002.170.00013 (Box 170)
  - NCAA Volley and Fhox, 2008; UA046.002.170.00014 (Box 170)
  - Tufts Athletics Tournament Materials, 2005 -- 2010; UA046.002.170.00015 (Box 170)
  - Homecoming, 2003; UA046.002.170.00016 (Box 170)
  - Homecoming, 2001; UA046.002.170.00017 (Box 170)
  - Homecoming, 2000; UA046.002.170.00018 (Box 170)
  - Barononian, 2008; UA046.002.170.00019 (Box 170)
  - Homecoming, 1997; UA046.002.170.00020 (Box 170)
  - John Baronian Tailgate Party RSVP Cards, 2008; UA046.002.170.00021 (Box 170)
  - Baseball - Clinic, 1990 -- 2004; UA046.002.170.00022 (Box 170)
  - Football, 1995 -- 2001; UA046.002.170.00023 (Box 170)
  - Equity Disclosure NCAA, 1995 -- 1998; UA046.002.170.00024 (Box 170)
  - Facilities, Renovations, Etc, 1996 -- 1997; UA046.002.170.00025 (Box 170)
  - Facilities Floor Plans, 1995; UA046.002.170.00026 (Box 170)
  - Scrapbooks - Softball, 2000 -- 2001; UA046.002.170.00027 (Box 170)
  - Softball, 1992 -- 2000; UA046.002.170.00028 (Box 170)
  - Varsity letter winners, 1960 -- 1961; UA046.002.170.00029 (Box 170)
  - Women's Soccer History, 1979 -- 1998; UA046.002.170.00030 (Box 170)
  - End of Year Reports - Women's Swim Team, 1980 -- 2012; UA046.002.170.00031 (Box 170)
  - Records and Awards [1 of 2, binder], 1982 -- 1988; UA046.002.171.00001 (Box 171)
  - Records and Awards [2 of 2, binder], 1982 -- 1988; UA046.002.171.00002 (Box 171)